在这篇文章中，我们将仔细观察
In this reading, we're going to look closely
如何定义抽象数据的相等操作
at how to define the equality operation for an abstract data
键入。
type.
读完这篇文章，你应该
After this reading, you should be
能够理解平等的定义
able to understand equality defined
就抽象功能而言，
in terms of the abstraction function,
作为等价关系，或作为观察。
as an equivalence relation, or as observations.
你也应该能够区分参考文献
You should also be able to differentiate between reference
平等与客体平等与区分
equality and object equality and differentiate
在严格的观测相等之间
between strict observational equality
以及可变类型的行为平等。
and behavioral equality for mutable types.
你应该能理解目标合同
And you should be able to understand the object contract
在Java中，能够正确实现等式
in Java and be able to implement equality correctly
对于可变和不可变类型。
for both mutable and immutable types.
我们开始吧。
Let's get started.